e-infin.com 2015-05-13

# Privacy Policy - E-Infinity Camera Store

HOMEPrivacy Policy

Privacy Policy

E-infin.com may collect site visitors’ information in the following ways: 

  * Account registration: The registration to the site is optional and data is stored in our server located in Hong Kong.
  * Order Placement: Your name, Physical Contact Address and Internet Contact Address to process the order will be collected.
  * Customer service interaction: we collect information when you interact with our customer service representative so as to accurately escalate your issue.
  * Survey or poll response: as our user, you may be invited to participate in surveys and pools from the E-infin.com and our affiliates.

1.PERSONAL INFORMATION USE

Personal information will be used to provide products or services requested by the customer, including product sales, repair and inspection, after-sales service, and newsletter distribution (Personal information includes such information necessary to understand the requirements of the customer such as a customer's purchase history and repair history).  
E-infinity is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We do not sell, trade or share to outside parties your personally identifiable information.  
We reserve the right to disclose your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

2.NEWSLETTER SUBSCRIPTION

E-infinity may offer free newsletters to inform you our product and promotion news. The subscription is defaulted to be done during email confirmation when you register the account. You may unsubscribe at any time. Instructions on how to opt-out come with every newsletter sent.

3.CHILDREN

We do not permit children under the age of 13 to register with us. If we discover that a user is under the age of 13, we will terminate the account and delete the user's information. Inherent in the E-infinity service is the responsibility of parents and/or guardians to ensure that their children's privacy is protected.

4.COOKIES

A cookie is a small amount of data which we send to your computer. The data is then stored on your browser or hard disk. We use cookies to personalize the website to your interests. We use cookies to help you remain logged into your account and to help us remember your browsing records so that we can better serve you in the future.  
You can change the browser setup so a notification will be sent to you when a cookie is received. You can decide whether to accept it or not.

5.SECURITY

We implement reasonable security measures to protect user information under our company’s control against loss, misuse or alteration.

6.THIRD PARTY LINKS

These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

7.LEGAL DISCLAIMER

We disclaim, and you agree, that E-infin.com. will not be liable to you for any damages caused by acts or events beyond our reasonable control including, without limitation, fires, floods, earthquake, acts of terrorism, wars, civil disturbances, governmental actions, and failures or delays of transportation that result in our disclosure of your personal information.

8.YOUR OBLIGATIONS

As a user, you have certain obligations to other users: You must, at all times, abide by the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights that may belong to third parties (such as trademarks or photographs). You must keep your username and password confidential and not share it with others.

9.YOUR CONSENT

By using our website, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

10.ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through E-infin.com and not to information collected offline. E-infinity reserves the right to modify any rules under privacy policy without prior notice.
